Robert Lancman

Junior Front End Developer (React)

570-607-998

@ robert.lancman@gmail.com

https://github.com/RobertLancman

Katowice



SUMMARY

Experienced trader enamored in Front-end.

With an eye toward entering the IT world professionally, I am developing myself by taking advantage of the many courses available on free and paid platforms. You can find the results of my efforts on my GitHub.

EXPERIENCE

Customer retention specialist

iii 02/2023 - Present ♀ Katowice

IT - Training Advisor

DAGMA Sp zoo

= 09/2021 - 12/2022

Katowice

Junior Front-End Developer (Angular)

TOM&CO

EDUCATION

High School

ZSOT - Lubliniec

iii 2008 - 2012 ♀ Lubliniec

LANGUAGES

Polish	Native	English	B2
Spanish	A1		

STRENGTHS

Team player



Ability to work under pressure



Willing to learn

TECH STACK

React(Redux)

Javascript

RESTful APIs

CSS/SASS

Webpack

Bootstrap

JIRA

HOBBY



Bushcraft

ı⊢ı Gym